CARLOS ANTHONY RODRIGUEZ

WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hello My name is Carlos, I am a collaborative problem solver with experience in front end development and design. I am able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

ILLUSTRATOR 2017 - 2022

Pirate Monkey Studio

- Engaged with clients, worked through a feedback loop to ensure illustrations were completed to specification and to deadline.
- Traveled to teach composition, design and other creative skills

TECHNICAL SERVICE MANAGER 2014 - 2016

T-Mobile

- Resolved hardware and software related issues through problem solving.
- Junior Trainer Internship I educated new employees to ensure confidence in ability.

CHEMICAL, BIOLOGICAL, RADIOLOGIC, AND NUCLEAR DEFENSE 2011 - 2015 United States Marine Corp

- In a team setting I worked in collaboration to ensure technical, strategic and physical capabilities in case of CRBN incident.
- Traveled teaching Marines proper use of HazMat equipment.

EDUCATION

FRONT END DEVELOPMENT, CODEFI WORKS 2022 - 2022

USMC CBRN SCHOOL 2011 - 2011

CAMDENTON HIGH SCHOOL 2005 - 2009

REFERENCES

- Christopher Lazzaro
- CIO, Associated Electric Cooperative Incorporated
- 417-848-6602

carlos.a.rodriguez8925@gmail.com

573-434-9494

Republic, Mo

github.com/Piratemonkey941

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- Angular
- GitHub
- Figma
- SCSS
- · Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Premier Pro
- Blender 3d

LANGUAGES

- Portugues
- Spanish